Register of the Yale Brozen papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Speeches and writings, 1942-1988 (Box 2-9)
  - Typescripts, 1942-1988 and undated
    - "An Economist's Worries About Current Policy: Politics Versus Prosperity," speech, Culver-Stockton College, Canton, Missouri, 1983 (Box-folder 6: 17)
    - "Merger Mania: Social Disease or Healthy Adaptation," speech, Clemens Chair in Economics Lecture, Saint John's University, Collegeville, Minnesota, 1984 (Box-folder 6: 18)
    - "Politics Versus Prosperity and Freedom", 1984 (Box-folder 6: 19)
    - "Vertical Restraints and Efficiency", 1984 (Box-folder 6: 20)
    - "The Economic Impact of Government Policy," speech, Economic Policy in the Market Process Symposium, the Netherlands, 1986 (Box-folder 6: 21)
    - "Will the Longest Peace Time Expansion Have a Sixth Birthday?" speech, 27th Annual Business Forecast Luncheon, Graduate School of Business, University of Chicago, 1987 (Box-folder 6: 22)
    - "A Worried Outlook for 1989," speech, 28th Annual Business Forecast Luncheon, Graduate School of Business, University of Chicago, 1988 (Box-folder 6: 23)
      Includes speech by Walter Fackler
  - Printed copies, 1943-1983
    Includes printed copies of Brozen's articles and speeches, including works published in The St. Croix Review. Arranged chronologically
    - Undated (Box-folder 6: 24-25)
    - 1943 (Box-folder 6: 26)
    - 1949 (Box-folder 6: 27)
    - 1950 (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 7: 2)
    - 1952 (Box-folder 7: 3)
    - 1953 (Box-folder 7: 4)
    - 1954 (Box-folder 7: 5-6)
    - 1955 (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - 1956 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - 1959 (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - 1960 (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - 1961 (Box-folder 7: 13)
    - 1962 (Box-folder 8: 1)
    - 1963 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - 1964 (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - 1966 (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 8: 6)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 8: 7)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 8: 8)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - 1974 (Box-folder 8: 13)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 8: 14)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 8: 15)
    - 1978 (Box-folder 9: 1)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 9: 2)
    - 1980 (Box-folder 9: 3)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 9: 4)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 9: 5)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 9: 6)
- Course materials, 1963-1986 (Box 9)
  Contains exams for courses taught by Brozen.
  - Business 300, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 9: 7)
  - Business 304, 1963, undated (Box-folder 9: 8)
  - Business 305, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 9: 9)
  - Business Economics, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 9: 10)